Academics Collection UA004
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Academics Collection
1856 -- 1996
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Miller, Russell E.
UA004
8.75 Linear Feet 18 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series: Academic.
Custodial History
The "Academic" collection was created by Russell Miller while preparing "Light on the Hill," his history of Tufts College. The material was assembled from various administrative departments. No attempt has been made to restore the original order of this material.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material compiled by Tufts University Historian Russell Miller relating to general academic matters that did not fit into any of his other subject categories. It contains artifacts, clippings, correspondence, fliers, notes, programs, photographs, press releases, speeches, and lists of presenters and recipients of academic honors. It contains materials on commencement, class day, convocation, and matriculation. In addition, it contains the full text of talks given as part of the Russell Lecture Series, a lecture series that was run through the Crane Theological School and is the University's oldest lecture series. There are also materials on the Steinman Poetry Lecture Series and the University Lecture Series.
The photographs are grouped at the end of the collection.
Biographical / Historical
Russell Elliott Miller was a Professor of History, University Historian and Archivist of Tufts University, and author of "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts College from 1852 to 1952" and the second volume "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts University since 1952." He was born in Bloomington, Minnesota, on April 25, 1916, to one of the last pioneer families in the Minnesota prairie. His mother spoke Dakota Sioux, which she had learned as a child. He received a B.A. in Education in 1937 and an M.A. in political science in 1939, both from the University of Florida at Gainesville. From 1942 to 1946, he served in the Army Air Corps as an enlisted man, rising to the rank of technical sergeant. Initially with personnel and classification, he was finally assigned to the historical section (intelligence) at the headquarters of the troop carrier command. In 1948 he earned a Master of Arts in history from Princeton University and came to Tufts that same year.
In 1952 he received a PhD from Princeton, and in 1964 Tufts appointed him Professor of History and University Historian and archivist. He taught courses ranging from the history of western civilization to the history of the American frontier. In 1966, he published "Light on the Hill, A History of Tufts College from 1852 to 1952." That year he received the Distinguished Service Award from the Tufts Alumni Association and became an honorary member of Phi Beta Kappa. In 1975 he became the Walter S. Dickson Professor of English and American History and chaired the Department of History from then until 1980. He was voted Emeritus Professor of English and American History in 1981 and received an honorary Doctor of Letters degree in 1983. In 1986, he completed the second volume of Tufts history, "Light on the Hill II, A History of Tufts University since 1952."
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Student Affairs and Services; Curriculum and Instruction -- Scholarships, Fellowships, Awards
- Academic, 1856 -- 1996; UA004.001; 8.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  The "Academic" collection was created by Russell Miller while preparing Light on the Hill, his history of Tufts College. It contains material relating to general academic matters that did not fit into any of his other subject categories. The material was assembled from various administrative departments. No attempt has been made to restore the original order of this material. This collection contains clippings, correspondence, programs, photographs, and lists of presenters and recipients of academic honors. It contains materials on commencement, class day, convocation, and matriculation. In addition, it contains the full text of talks given as part of the Russell Lecture Series, a lecture series run through the Crane Theological School and the university's oldest lecture series. There are materials present on the Steinman Poetry Lecture Series and the University Lecture Series. The photographs are grouped at the end of the collection.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Academic Honors, 1887 -- 1933; UA004.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - Academic Honors, 1934 -- 1952; UA004.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Academic Honors, 1953 -- 1958; UA004.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Academic Honors, 1959 -- 1962; UA004.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Academic Honors, 1963 -- 1965; UA004.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Academic Honors, 1966 -- 1967; UA004.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Academic Honors, 1968 -- 1978; UA004.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Academic Awards, Committee on, 1937 -- 1968; UA004.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Academic Regalia, 1902; UA004.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Anniversaries and celebrations, 1914 -- 1956; UA004.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Baccalaureate addresses, 1914 -- 1956; UA004.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Ballou Medal, 1939 -- 1992; UA004.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Academic Centenial, 1952; UA004.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Tickets, programs, and map, donated by Doane University UA-2023-016.
  - Academic Centenial pageant, 1952; UA004.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Academic Centennial, 1952; UA004.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Centennial Celebration map, 1952; UA004.000338 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Donated by Doane University, UA-2023-016.
  - Academic Centennial Pageant, 1952; UA004.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - College and class colors, 1904 -- 1960; UA004.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - College seal and shield, 1878 -- 1966; UA004.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Academic Commencements (General), 1930 -- 1964; UA004.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1862; UA004.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1857; UA004.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1863; UA004.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1864; UA004.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1865; UA004.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1866; UA004.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1867; UA004.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1868; UA004.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1869; UA004.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1870; UA004.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1871; UA004.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1872; UA004.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1873; UA004.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1874; UA004.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1875; UA004.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1876; UA004.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1877; UA004.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1878; UA004.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1879; UA004.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1880; UA004.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1881; UA004.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1882; UA004.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1883; UA004.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1884; UA004.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1885; UA004.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1886; UA004.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1887; UA004.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1888; UA004.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1889; UA004.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1890; UA004.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1891; UA004.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1892; UA004.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1893; UA004.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1894; UA004.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1895; UA004.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1896; UA004.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1897; UA004.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1898; UA004.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1899; UA004.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1900; UA004.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1901; UA004.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - Academic Commencement, 1902; UA004.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1903; UA004.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1904; UA004.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1905; UA004.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1906; UA004.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1907; UA004.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1908; UA004.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1909; UA004.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1910; UA004.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1911; UA004.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1912; UA004.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1913; UA004.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1915; UA004.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1916; UA004.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1917; UA004.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1918; UA004.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1919; UA004.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1920; UA004.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1921; UA004.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1922; UA004.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1923; UA004.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1924; UA004.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1925; UA004.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1926; UA004.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1927; UA004.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1928; UA004.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1929; UA004.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1930; UA004.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1931; UA004.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1932; UA004.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1933; UA004.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Academic Commencement, 1934; UA004.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1935; UA004.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1936; UA004.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1937; UA004.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1938; UA004.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1939; UA004.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1940; UA004.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1941; UA004.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1942; UA004.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1943; UA004.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1944; UA004.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1945; UA004.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1946; UA004.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1947; UA004.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Academic Commencement, 1948; UA004.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1949; UA004.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1950; UA004.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1951; UA004.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1952; UA004.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1953; UA004.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1954; UA004.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1955; UA004.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1956; UA004.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1957; UA004.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1958; UA004.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1959; UA004.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1960; UA004.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1961; UA004.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1962; UA004.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Academic Commencement, 1963; UA004.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1964; UA004.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1965; UA004.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1966; UA004.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1967; UA004.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1968; UA004.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1969; UA004.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1970; UA004.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1971; UA004.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1972; UA004.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1973; UA004.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1974; UA004.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1975; UA004.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1976; UA004.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1977; UA004.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1978; UA004.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1979; UA004.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Academic Commencement, 1980; UA004.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1981; UA004.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1982; UA004.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1983; UA004.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1984; UA004.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1985; UA004.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1986; UA004.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1987; UA004.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1988; UA004.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1989; UA004.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1992; UA004.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1993; UA004.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1994; UA004.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1990; UA004.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Academic Commencement, 1991; UA004.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Convocation, 1928 -- 1955; UA004.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Convocation, 1955; UA004.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Convocation, 1955; UA004.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Convocation, 1955; UA004.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Diplomas and degrees, 1908 -- 1984; UA004.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Goddard prizes, 1877 -- 1947; UA004.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Mace, 1938; UA004.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Matriculation convocations, 1949 -- 1996; UA004.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Commencement clippings, 1856 -- 1969; UA004.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Parents council, 1976 -- 1978; UA004.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Parents day/weekend, 1964 -- 1993; UA004.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Prize competitions, 1933 -- 1946; UA004.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Public lectures, 1916 -- 1975; UA004.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1867 -- 1973; UA004.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1868; UA004.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1869; UA004.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1870; UA004.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1871; UA004.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1872; UA004.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1873; UA004.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Russell lectures, 1874; UA004.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1875; UA004.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1876; UA004.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1877; UA004.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1878; UA004.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1879; UA004.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1880; UA004.001.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1881; UA004.001.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1882; UA004.001.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1883; UA004.001.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1884; UA004.001.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1885; UA004.001.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1886; UA004.001.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1887; UA004.001.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1888; UA004.001.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1889; UA004.001.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Russell lectures, 1890; UA004.001.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1891; UA004.001.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1893; UA004.001.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1894; UA004.001.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1896; UA004.001.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1897; UA004.001.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1898; UA004.001.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1899; UA004.001.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1900; UA004.001.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1901; UA004.001.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1902; UA004.001.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1903; UA004.001.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1904; UA004.001.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1905; UA004.001.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1906; UA004.001.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1907; UA004.001.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1908; UA004.001.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1909; UA004.001.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1910; UA004.001.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1911; UA004.001.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1912; UA004.001.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Russell lectures, 1913; UA004.001.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1914; UA004.001.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1916; UA004.001.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1917; UA004.001.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1919; UA004.001.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1921; UA004.001.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1922; UA004.001.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1927; UA004.001.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1928; UA004.001.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1930; UA004.001.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1931; UA004.001.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1932; UA004.001.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1933; UA004.001.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1934; UA004.001.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1935; UA004.001.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1936; UA004.001.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1937; UA004.001.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1938; UA004.001.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1940; UA004.001.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1941; UA004.001.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1943; UA004.001.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1944; UA004.001.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1945; UA004.001.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1946; UA004.001.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1947; UA004.001.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1948; UA004.001.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1949; UA004.001.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1950; UA004.001.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1951; UA004.001.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1952; UA004.001.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1953; UA004.001.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1954; UA004.001.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1955; UA004.001.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1956; UA004.001.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1957; UA004.001.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1958; UA004.001.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1959; UA004.001.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1960; UA004.001.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1961; UA004.001.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1962; UA004.001.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Russell lectures, 1965; UA004.001.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1966; UA004.001.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1967; UA004.001.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1968; UA004.001.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1972; UA004.001.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1976; UA004.001.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1980; UA004.001.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1982; UA004.001.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Russell lectures, 1983; UA004.001.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Semi-Centennial, 1902; UA004.001.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Steinman poetry lectures, 1958 -- 1960; UA004.001.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - University lectures, 1939 -- 1973; UA004.001.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Photographs, 1876 -- 1983; UA004.001.016
    - Commencement, 1876; UA004.001.016.00001 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1913; UA004.001.016.00002 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1914; UA004.001.016.00003 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1919; UA004.001.016.00004 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1920; UA004.001.016.00005 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1923; UA004.001.016.00006 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1924; UA004.001.016.00007 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1926; UA004.001.016.00008 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1927; UA004.001.016.00009 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1930; UA004.001.016.00010 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1931; UA004.001.016.00011 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1932; UA004.001.016.00012 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1935; UA004.001.016.00013 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1936; UA004.001.016.00014 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1939; UA004.001.016.00015 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1940; UA004.001.016.00016 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1941; UA004.001.016.00017 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1944; UA004.001.016.00018 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1945; UA004.001.016.00019 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1946; UA004.001.016.00020 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1947; UA004.001.016.00021 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1948; UA004.001.016.00022 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1949; UA004.001.016.00023 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1950; UA004.001.016.00024 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1951; UA004.001.016.00025 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1952; UA004.001.016.00026 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1953; UA004.001.016.00027 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1954; UA004.001.016.00028 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1955; UA004.001.016.00029 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1956; UA004.001.016.00030 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1957; UA004.001.016.00031 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1958; UA004.001.016.00032 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1959; UA004.001.016.00033 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1959; UA004.001.016.00034 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1962; UA004.001.016.00035 (Box 16)
    - Commencement, 1963; UA004.001.016.00036 (Box 16)
    - Academic honors: photos, 1938 -- 1966; UA004.001.017.00001 (Box 17)
    - Baccalaureate addresses, 1953; UA004.001.017.00002 (Box 17)
    - Centennial, 1952; UA004.001.017.00003 (Box 17)
    - Centennial pageant, 1950; UA004.001.017.00004 (Box 17)
    - College seal, 1936 -- 1964; UA004.001.017.00005 (Box 17)
    - Convocation, 1946 -- 1955; UA004.001.017.00006 (Box 17)
    - Lectures: Demity Muranier, 1963; UA004.001.017.00007 (Box 17)
    - Mace, 1938; UA004.001.017.00008 (Box 17)
    - Parents Day, 1956 -- 1962; UA004.001.017.00009 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Medal, 1961 -- 1962; UA004.001.017.00010 (Box 17)
    - Russel Lecturer: Laurens Hickok Seelye, 1936; UA004.001.017.00011 (Box 17)
    - James Russell, n.d., UA004.001.017.00012 (Box 17)
    - David B. Steinman, n.d., UA004.001.017.00013 (Box 17)
    - Commencement, 1959; UA004.001.018.00001 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1960; UA004.001.018.00002 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1961; UA004.001.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1962; UA004.001.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1963; UA004.001.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - Commencement: slides, 1964; UA004.001.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - Commencement: prints, 1964; UA004.001.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1965; UA004.001.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1966; UA004.001.018.00009 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1968; UA004.001.018.00010 (Box 18)